const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    category: "Animals",
    question: "Largest land animal",
    answer: "elephant"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    category: "Countries",
    question: "Capital of France",
    answer: "paris"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    category: "Movies",
    question: "Science fiction film with a space station",
    answer: "gravity"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    category: "Fruits",
    question: "Yellow fruit, known for its curved shape",
    answer: "banana"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    category: "Colors",
    question: "A mixture of red and blue",
    answer: "purple"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    category: "Sports",
    question: "Game with a round ball and goals",
    answer: "soccer"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    category: "Food",
    question: "Italian dish with layers of pasta and cheese",
    answer: "lasagna"
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    category: "Technology",
    question: "Popular smartphone brand",
    answer: "iphone"
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    category: "Space",
    question: "Closest star to Earth",
    answer: "sun"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    category: "Music",
    question: "Legendary rock band from Liverpool",
    answer: "beatles"
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    category: "Vegetables",
    question: "Green vegetable often used in salads",
    answer: "lettuce"
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    category: "Cities",
    question: "Capital of Japan",
    answer: "tokyo"
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    category: "Instruments",
    question: "String instrument with six strings",
    answer: "guitar"
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    category: "History",
    question: "Ancient Egyptian queen",
    answer: "cleopatra"
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    category: "Transportation",
    question: "Two-wheeled vehicle powered by pedals",
    answer: "bicycle"
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    category: "Books",
    question: "Author of 'Harry Potter' series",
    answer: "rowling"
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    category: "Weather",
    question: "Natural disaster with strong winds and rain",
    answer: "hurricane"
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    category: "Body Parts",
    question: "Organ responsible for pumping blood",
    answer: "heart"
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    category: "Plants",
    question: "Tall woody plant often found in forests",
    answer: "tree"
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    category: "Mammals",
    question: "Large marine mammal with tusks",
    answer: "walrus"
  }
];

export default questions;
